在席議員以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。
根據藥劑業及毒藥條例，就批准《二零一四年藥劑業及毒藥修訂規例》及《二零一四年毒藥表修訂規例》動議嘅議議決議案。咁要發言嘅議員，請你按下要求發言按鈕，然後請食物及衞生局局長發言及動議議案。
主席，我動議該動議，以我名義印在議程上，請通過。
Currently, we regulate the sale and supply of pharmaceutical products through a registration and monitoring system set up in accordance with the Pharmacy and Poisons Ordinance.
The ordinance maintains several schedules under the pharmacy and poison speculations, and the poison list under the poison list speculations.
pharmaceutical products put under different parts of the poisons list and different schedules are subject to different levels of control in regard to the conditions of sale and keeping of records.
為保護公共健康，某些藥品產品，只能在藥局在監督下由註冊藥師售出，並在他們的在場。
For certain pharmaceutical products, proper records of the particulars of the sales must be kept.
包括日期、售出，的名稱及地址、的買家，的名稱及數量、的藥物，及目的，為何需要。
The sale of some pharmaceutical products must be authorised by prescription from a registered medical practitioner, dentist or veterinary surgeon.
arising from an application for registration of seven pharmaceutical products.
The pharmacy and poisons board.
propose to add the following substance to Part One of the poisons list.
And the first and third schedules to the pharmacy and poison speculations.
A，five and minor levulinic acid，its source，its derivatives，their source。
B，cobisette，是source。
C，L. Vitigravia is sauce.
D，呢是sanitite，E。
咪肥磚，啲酸，啲esters，啲酸。
F。
帕蘭佩爾。
and G。
Patsumap。
藥物產品含上述七種物質，必須。
他 sold in pharmacies under the supervision of registered pharmacists and in their presence.
with the support of prescriptions.
For amendment regulations concerning the adding of the above seven substances to Part One of the Poisons List and the first and third schedule to the Pharmacy and Poison Regulations, we propose them to take immediate effect upon gazette on the 21st March, 2014.
to allow early control and sale of the relevant medicines.
The two amendment regulations are made by the Pharmsin's Poison Board, which is a statutory authority established under the ordinance to regulate pharmaceutical products.
The board comprises members engaged in the pharmacy, medical and academic professions.
The board considers the proposed amendment necessary in view of the potency, toxicity and potential side effects of the medicines concerned.
With these remarks, Mr. President, I hope members could support the motion. Thank you.
現在各位提出嘅代議議題係食物及衞生局局長動議嘅議案，予以通過。咁有冇議員要發言？
咁兩位提出上述代決議題，附諸表決，贊成嘅請舉手。
反對嘅請舉手。我認為議題獲得在席議員以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。
以怨以安。